directspace.net 2010-06-11

# DirectSpace Networks | Dedicated Servers, Colocation and VPS Services

Privacy Policy Last Modified - 06/01/2009

**Website Visitors-**

What information do we collect? 

When you visit our Web site, our Web server collects basic user information about you that includes your ISP's domain, the time you accessed our Web site, and the pages from within our Web site that you visit and is not personally identifiable information except as needed to prevent fraud or abuse of the system. 

We may at times also use cookies, which are small pieces of information that a Web site can store in a designated file on your computer. Cookies allow a Web application to respond to you as an individual. By gathering and remembering information about your preferences, the Web application can tailor its operation to your needs, likes, and dislikes. Most web browsers allow you to control this use of cookies. Please take a look at your particular browser for instructions on this function. If you elect to disable cookies, please keep in mind that you will not be able to take full advantage of a personalized experience on our Web site. It is possible that some portions of the site will not function properly or may perform more slowly if you choose to reject cookies. 

Our Web site allows for a chat function. Chat functions allow you to participate in “live” online conversations with us on our Web site. Although the transcripts from the chats may be stored internally on in-house servers for our records only, we collect no personally identifiable information about you when you participate unless you choose to provide that information to us. 

How do we use this information? 

The basic user information collected is used to help us analyze Web traffic, improve the content of our Web site and improve your experience on our Web site. 

Our Web site provides links to other Web sites, sites that may be maintained by companies that are not affiliates of ours. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites and we encourage you to use caution. In particular, we recommend that you view the privacy policy posted on each site to confirm the sites policies are acceptable to you. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this site. 

Directspace Networks Customers- 

What information do we collect? 

When you sign up for DirectSpace Networks' services, you provide us with both contact and payment information. Contact information typically includes your name, address, and phone number. Payment information typically includes your credit card number. 

While you are a DirectSpace Networks customer, we manage information with regard to your account status, choice of services, and customer logs. In addition, we may store customers' electronic mail and other communications as a necessary incident to the transmission and delivery of those communications. 

How do we use this information? 

We use the contact information you provide us to establish our service for you. We use payment information for payment processing purposes only. We create and maintain other information such as customer account status, choice of services, and customer logs in the normal course of providing service. 

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you to log into one of our secure sites with your customer identification. In order to complete the referral email form inviting your friend to visit the site, you will be required to enter your email address as well as the email address for your friend. We do not store this information, except as necessary to send the email through normal email protocols.
